<story-context id="4-2-performance-data-settings" v="1.0">
  <metadata>
    <epicId>4</epicId>
    <storyId>2</storyId>
    <title>Performance & Data Settings</title>
    <status>ready-for-dev</status>
    <generatedAt>2025-12-15</generatedAt>
    <generator>BMAD Story Context Workflow (Regenerated)</generator>
    <sourceStoryPath>docs/sprint-artifacts/4-2-Performance & Data Settings.md</sourceStoryPath>
  </metadata>
  <story>
    <asA>user</asA>
    <iWant>to manage offline mode and data synchronization settings</iWant>
    <soThat>I can control my app's behavior in various network conditions and manage local data.</soThat>
    <tasks>
      - Frontend (apps/web):
        - UI Implementation (Flow 17, Screen 1-4): Create React components for the "Performance & Data" settings sub-screen.
        - Offline Mode Logic: Implement client-side logic for enabling/disabling offline mode, caching daily plans and workout logs.
        - Synchronization Logic: Develop logic for detecting network connectivity changes and automatically/manually syncing offline data.
        - Local Cache Management: Implement functionality for clearing the local cache with user confirmation.
        - API Integration: Ensure robust API calls to the FastAPI backend for data synchronization.
        - Testing: Write unit tests, integration tests, and Playwright E2E tests.
      - Backend (apps/api):
        - API Endpoint Enhancement: Ensure the `/logs` endpoint (from Story 2.4) can handle incremental data synchronization.
        - Testing: Write integration tests for the `/logs` endpoint.
      - Refinement: Ensure UI adheres to `ux_design_content` principles, implement structured JSON logging, verify consistency with naming conventions.
    </tasks>
  </story>
  <acceptanceCriteria>
    <criterion>AC4.2.1: The "Performance & Data" settings sub-screen is accessible.</criterion>
    <criterion>AC4.2.2: Toggling "Offline Mode" switches between online and offline functionality, caching data locally.</criterion>
    <criterion>AC4.2.3: "Auto-Sync Offline Data" toggle controls automatic synchronization upon reconnection.</criterion>
    <criterion>AC4.2.4: Tapping "[ Clear Local Cache ]" prompts for confirmation and then clears local cached data.</criterion>
    <criterion>AC4.2.5: An offline status indicator is displayed in the main app UI when offline.</criterion>
    <criterion>AC4.2.6: A "Sync Now" button/prompt appears when connection is restored and unsynced data exists.</criterion>
  </acceptanceCriteria>
  <artifacts>
    <docs>
        <doc>
            <path>docs/architecture.md</path>
            <title>Architecture</title>
            <section>Performance Considerations</section>
            <snippet>Frontend: Code Splitting, Lazy Loading, Image Optimization.</snippet>
        </doc>
        <doc>
            <path>docs/ux-design-direction.md</path>
            <title>UX Design Direction</title>
            <section>Flow 17: Toggle Offline Mode & Resume Sync</section>
            <snippet>Guides the implementation of offline functionality, clear status indicators, and sync mechanisms.</snippet>
        </doc>
    </docs>
    <code>
      <!-- No existing code artifacts found relevant to this story. -->
    </code>
  </artifacts>
  <constraints>
    <constraint>The frontend must persist the active workout state in local storage to prevent data loss.</constraint>
    <constraint>Backend `/logs` endpoint must handle incremental data synchronization from offline mode, including conflict resolution.</constraint>
  </constraints>
  <interfaces>
      <interface>
        <name>Workout Logs API</name>
        <kind>REST Endpoint</kind>
        <signature>POST /logs</signature>
        <path>apps/api/app/api/logs.py</path>
      </interface>
  </interfaces>
  <tests>
      <standards>Unit tests for components, offline logic, and sync; integration tests for local storage and API calls; E2E tests for full offline/sync user flows.</standards>
      <locations><location>apps/web/src/app/settings/performance/</location></locations>
      <ideas>
          <idea>Unit test offline mode toggle and local caching logic.</idea>
          <idea>E2E test the full offline/sync user flow, including network interruption simulation and data recovery.</idea>
      </ideas>
  </tests>
</story-context>